{"qid": "easy-agenda-0000", "question": "When did Grace attend Broadway Show on 2022/02/17?", "answer": "8:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0001", "question": "How long did Charles attend Watch a baseball game on 2022/05/21?", "answer": "3:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0002", "question": "How long did Henry attend Chili cook-off on 2022/03/21?", "answer": "3:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0003", "question": "Who attended Boxing match between 7:00 PM and 10:00 PM on 2022/11/06 in Madison Square Garden ?", "answer": "Joseph"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0004", "question": "Where did Poetry reading that George attended take place on 2022/09/26?", "answer": "The Poetry Foundation"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0005", "question": "When did Mia attend Choral Performance on 2022/01/05?", "answer": "1:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0006", "question": "What did Amelia do from 4:00 PM to 6:00 PM on 2022/02/23?", "answer": "Parkour Class"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0007", "question": "How long did Brian attend Happy Hour on 2022/06/20?", "answer": "2:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0008", "question": "How long did Daisy attend Public policy conference on 2022/02/25?", "answer": "8:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0009", "question": "When did Brian attend Car maintenance check on 2022/06/30?", "answer": "9:00 AM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0010", "question": "What did Daisy do from 11:00 PM to 1:00 AM on 2022/02/01?", "answer": "Late Night Movie"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0011", "question": "Where did Morning Swim that Matilda attended take place on 2022/07/24?", "answer": "LA Fitness Aquatic Center "}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0012", "question": "What did Thomas do from 8:00 PM to 10:00 PM on 2022/10/03?", "answer": "Star-gazing"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0013", "question": "When did Millie attend Wine education seminar on 2022/06/11?", "answer": "6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0014", "question": "Where did Farmers Market Visit that Molly attended take place on 2022/03/05?", "answer": "Union Square Greenmarket"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0015", "question": "How long did Millie attend Theatre play on 2022/12/07?", "answer": "2:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0016", "question": "Who attended Aquarium visit between 10:00 AM and 5:00 PM on 2022/07/06 in New England Aquarium?", "answer": "Georgina"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0017", "question": "Where did Ballet Performance that Ruby attended take place on 2022/06/21?", "answer": "Ballet Theater, Music Center"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0018", "question": "Where did Martial arts class that Lily attended take place on 2022/10/11?", "answer": "The Martial Arts Academy"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0019", "question": "When did Robert attend Opera Performance on 2022/04/18?", "answer": "7:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0020", "question": "Who attended Coffee tasting between 10:00 AM and 11:00 AM on 2022/12/08 in Cafe Grumpy?", "answer": "George"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0021", "question": "Who attended Photography Class between 11:00 AM and 1:00 PM on 2022/03/09 in The Camera Store ?", "answer": "Chloe"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0022", "question": "Who attended Wine and Paint Event between 6:00 PM and 8:00 PM on 2022/04/10 in Art Studio Downtown?", "answer": "Benjamin"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0023", "question": "How long did Willow attend Summer camp informational session on 2022/04/02?", "answer": "1:30:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0024", "question": "When did Elsie attend Speed dating event on 2022/10/12?", "answer": "7:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0025", "question": "What did Richard do from 1:00 PM to 3:00 PM on 2022/03/26?", "answer": "Roller skating"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0026", "question": "Where did Chess club meeting that Victoria attended take place on 2022/06/13?", "answer": "The Chess Forum"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0027", "question": "Who attended Graduation ceremony between 5:00 PM and 7:00 PM on 2022/10/22 in Stadium, University of North Carolina?", "answer": "Freya"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0028", "question": "Where did Culinary festival that Adrian attended take place on 2022/09/27?", "answer": "The Convention Center "}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0029", "question": "What did Isabella do from 2:00 PM to 4:00 PM on 2022/12/25?", "answer": "Batting cage practice"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0030", "question": "Who attended Star Gazing between 8:00 PM and 11:00 PM on 2022/08/23 in Observatory, Griffith Park Observatory?", "answer": "Adrian"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0031", "question": "Who attended Horse race between 2:00 PM and 5:00 PM on 2022/08/14 in Santa Anita Park?", "answer": "Harper"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0032", "question": "How long did George attend Tennis lesson on 2022/06/22?", "answer": "1:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0033", "question": "When did Georgia attend Move-in day on 2022/06/22?", "answer": "9:00 AM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0034", "question": "What did Grace do from 8:00 PM to 9:30 PM on 2022/08/01?", "answer": "Stand-up comedy show"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0035", "question": "How long did Natalie attend Volunteer work on 2022/03/01?", "answer": "4:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0036", "question": "How long did Daisy attend Jazz Performance on 2022/02/05?", "answer": "3:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0037", "question": "What did Andrew do from 6:00 PM to 8:00 PM on 2022/08/23?", "answer": "Fashion show"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0038", "question": "What did Charlotte do from 4:00 PM to 5:30 PM on 2022/10/31?", "answer": "Cooking Class"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0039", "question": "What did Elizabeth do from 7:30 PM to 10:00 PM on 2022/06/29?", "answer": "Opera performance"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0040", "question": "Where did Movie Night that Hector attended take place on 2022/06/03?", "answer": "The Standard Hotel rooftop "}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0041", "question": "Who attended Gym workout between 2:00 PM and 3:00 PM on 2022/03/15 in CrossFit Fitness?", "answer": "Brian"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0042", "question": "What did Alice do from 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM on 2022/07/28?", "answer": "Fashion Show"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0043", "question": "What did Amelia do from 07:00 PM to 09:00 PM on 2022/08/07?", "answer": "Language Exchange"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0044", "question": "When did Georgina attend Corporate Social Responsibility Conference on 2022/04/23?", "answer": "10:00 AM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0045", "question": "How long did Albert attend Conference Call on 2022/04/24?", "answer": "1:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0046", "question": "Where did Historical Tour that Matilda attended take place on 2022/12/13?", "answer": "Local History Museum"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0047", "question": "When did Phillip attend Creative writing workshop on 2022/06/28?", "answer": "6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0048", "question": "When did Felix attend Live piano performance on 2022/03/30?", "answer": "7:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0049", "question": "Where did Robotics seminar that Esme attended take place on 2022/09/13?", "answer": "University Auditorium"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0050", "question": "When did Benjamin attend Movie night on 2022/10/21?", "answer": "8:30 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0051", "question": "How long did Daisy attend Stand-up paddleboarding lesson on 2022/10/19?", "answer": "1:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0052", "question": "When did Aidan attend Bird-watching tour on 2022/12/09?", "answer": "8:00 AM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0053", "question": "How long did Aidan attend Leadership training on 2022/09/12?", "answer": "8:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0054", "question": "What did Ava do from 9:00 AM to 5:00 PM on 2022/06/07?", "answer": "Industry conference"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0055", "question": "What did Isabella do from 2:00 PM to 3:00 PM on 2022/12/03?", "answer": "Ballet class"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0056", "question": "When did Faith attend Ice hockey game on 2022/10/04?", "answer": "7:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0057", "question": "How long did Joshua attend Horseback riding on 2022/09/11?", "answer": "2:30:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0058", "question": "How long did Daniel attend Dance Class on 2022/06/24?", "answer": "1:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0059", "question": "What did Anthony do from 8:00 AM to 10:00 AM on 2022/09/04?", "answer": "Classic Car Show"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0060", "question": "Who attended Poetry reading between 7:00 PM and 9:00 PM on 2022/04/07 in Beyond Baroque?", "answer": "Charlotte"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0061", "question": "How long did Aurora attend Dreamcatcher-making workshop on 2022/01/24?", "answer": "2:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0062", "question": "When did Georgina attend Indie film festival on 2022/04/30?", "answer": "12:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0063", "question": "How long did Adam attend Breakfast meeting on 2022/05/07?", "answer": "1:30:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0064", "question": "What did Aurora do from 2:00 PM to 3:00 PM on 2022/02/21?", "answer": "Meeting with a client"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0065", "question": "When did Willow attend Intermediate Spanish conversation class on 2022/09/26?", "answer": "11:00 AM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0066", "question": "What did Matilda do from 7:30 PM to 9:30 PM on 2022/03/25?", "answer": "Opera show"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0067", "question": "How long did Matilda attend Food truck festival on 2022/12/26?", "answer": "5:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0068", "question": "Where did Floral design session that Emily attended take place on 2022/09/30?", "answer": "Garden Collage"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0069", "question": "How long did Brian attend Movie Screening on 2022/05/22?", "answer": "2:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0070", "question": "When did Patrick attend Landscape photography workshop on 2022/02/22?", "answer": "8:00 AM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0071", "question": "When did Georgia attend Escape Room on 2022/06/24?", "answer": "6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0072", "question": "When did Phoebe attend Food festival on 2022/01/10?", "answer": "6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0073", "question": "What did Emily do from 7:00 PM to 9:30 PM on 2022/02/07?", "answer": "Board game night"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0074", "question": "When did Georgina attend Pet grooming session on 2022/04/18?", "answer": "1:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0075", "question": "How long did Anthony attend Volleyball Tournament on 2022/11/13?", "answer": "3:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0076", "question": "When did Albert attend Youth talent showcase on 2022/08/11?", "answer": "5:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0077", "question": "Where did Charity auction that Willow attended take place on 2022/06/25?", "answer": "Sotheby's Auction House"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0078", "question": "Where did Fun run that Zara attended take place on 2022/02/19?", "answer": "The Fun Run Trail"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0079", "question": "When did Layla attend Take a pottery throwing class on 2022/04/24?", "answer": "10:00 AM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0080", "question": "What did James do from 9:00 AM to 11:00 AM on 2022/02/02?", "answer": "Business meeting"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0081", "question": "What did Georgina do from 1:00 PM to 11:00 PM on 2022/05/18?", "answer": "Oktoberfest"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0082", "question": "When did Emily attend Visit to historic landmark on 2022/05/30?", "answer": "10:00 AM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0083", "question": "Who attended Wine Tasting between 5:00 PM and 7:00 PM on 2022/05/23 in City Winery?", "answer": "Penelope"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0084", "question": "What did Ava do from 12:00 PM to 4:00 PM on 2022/06/16?", "answer": "Cooking competition"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0085", "question": "When did Isabella attend Photography workshop on 2022/05/06?", "answer": "12:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0086", "question": "How long did Faith attend Brewery tasting room on 2022/12/06?", "answer": "2:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0087", "question": "Who attended Art exhibit opening reception between 5:00 PM and 7:00 PM on 2022/08/01 in Locust Projects, Design District?", "answer": "Sophia"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0088", "question": "When did Faith attend Book club meeting on 2022/03/26?", "answer": "7:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0089", "question": "How long did Charlotte attend Piano Recital on 2022/01/30?", "answer": "2:00:00"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0090", "question": "Where did Intermediate Spanish lesson that Alice attended take place on 2022/05/20?", "answer": "Instituto Cervantes"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0091", "question": "Who attended Historical lecture between 7:00 PM and 9:00 PM on 2022/11/29 in The New-York Historical Society?", "answer": "Henry"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0092", "question": "When did Emily attend Jazz concert on 2022/06/15?", "answer": "8:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0093", "question": "Where did Live podcast that Hector attended take place on 2022/06/15?", "answer": "The Bell House"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0094", "question": "When did Thomas attend Artisanal Pizza Making on 2022/10/28?", "answer": "6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0095", "question": "When did Thomas attend Model airplane flying on 2022/03/18?", "answer": "10:00 AM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0096", "question": "When did William attend Music concert on 2022/01/17?", "answer": "8:00 PM"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0097", "question": "What did Lily do from 7:00 PM to 9:00 PM on 2022/10/06?", "answer": "Cocktail making class"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0098", "question": "What did Adam do from 7:00 PM to 9:00 PM on 2022/10/27?", "answer": "Join a public speaking class"}
{"qid": "easy-agenda-0099", "question": "When did Madison attend Stand-up comedy show on 2022/10/11?", "answer": "8:00 PM"}
